greencupboards.com 2018-09-07

# Privacy Policy - etailz, Inc.

### PRIVACY POLICY

This Privacy Policy aims to give you information regarding how etailz collects and uses your personal data through your use of our website. Personal data is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. It is important that you read this Privacy Policy so that you are fully aware of how we collect, use, protect, or otherwise handle your personal data. This Privacy Policy applies to all websites owned and operated by etailz, Inc. (“we”, “us”, “our”); it does not apply to the practices of companies etailz does not own or control.

When you visit our website, you have choices about whether to provide us with information and how we use that information. You may choose not to provide us with information, but your choice(s) may prevent you from contacting etailz directly or limit your use of certain features. For example, if you do not provide us with an email address we cannot respond to your inquiry.

We may update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes in the law, our services, our companies, or advances in technology. We will alert you to this change by placing a notice on our website or sending an email. Our use of the information we collect is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used.

### INFORMATION WE COLLECT & USE

Some of the information we collect is provided by you, some is collected automatically, and some may be collected from other sources.  

#### Information You Provide

When you use our website, you may submit an inquiry request to etailz and will be asked for the following personal information:

  * Name
  * Email Address
  * Phone Number
  * Company Name
  * Additional information you voluntarily provide

#### Information We Automatically Collect

We automatically collect certain information to help us understand how visitors use our website. For example, each time you visit our website we automatically collect your IP address, location information, browser and computer type, access time, the webpage from which you came, and the webpage(s) that you access during your visit.  

#### Analytics

We may use Google Analytics or other providers to understand better how individuals and their devices interact with the Services. Learn more about [how Google uses data when you visit a partner site or app](https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites).  

#### Cookies and Related Technologies

We also use cookies (which are small amounts of data sent from a web server to your browser that are stored on your computer hard drive) to validate your identity, tailor our website to meet your personal interests, improve the quality of our website, or learn about your online activity and preferences. Generally, you can set your browser not to accept cookies or to notify you if you are sent a cookie, giving you the opportunity to choose whether or not to accept the cookie.  

#### Plug-Ins

Our websites may offer you the ability to interact with plugins from websites, which allows etailz and/or that website to receive data from or about you. In some cases, we may know that you clicked on a plugin.  

### HOW WE USE INFORMATION & LAWFUL BASES

We will only use your personal data when the law allows us to. Most commonly, we will use your personal data to provide you requested information, respond to a survey or marketing communication, or respond to your customer service requests.

For purposes of European Union data protection laws, we process personal data where:

  * We need to perform the contract we are about to enter into or have entered into with you, such as when we process a payment
  * It is in our legitimate interests (or those of a third party) and your data protection interests and fundamental rights and freedoms do not override those interests, such as when we secure the services, engage in fraud prevention, and direct marketing
  * We need to comply with a legal or regulatory obligation
  * We have your consent to do so. We do not generally rely on consent as a lawful basis for processing your personal data, but you have the right to withdraw consent to marketing at any time by contacting us.

We may combine the information we collect (“aggregate”) or remove pieces of information (“de-identify”) to limit or prevent identification of any particular user or device, which can help support our research and marketing efforts. This Privacy Policy does not apply to our use of such aggregated or de-identified information.  

### LOCATION OF DATA PROCESSING

Information that we collect and use is processed in the United States. By accessing our website, you acknowledge that your information will be processed as described in this Privacy Policy.  

### HOW WE PROTECT YOUR DATA

We have implemented appropriate security measures to prevent your personal data from being accidentally lost, used or accessed in an unauthorized way, altered or disclosed. In addition, we limit access to your personal data to a limited number of employees, agents, contractors and other third parties who have a business need to know. They will only process your personal data on our instructions and they are subject to a duty of confidentiality.

We have put in place procedures to deal with any suspected personal data breach and will notify you and any applicable regulator of a breach where we are legally required to do so.  

### THIRD PARTY DISCLOSURE

We do not rent, sell or share information except as described in this Privacy Policy. We may share your personal data with service providers and other third parties if necessary to fulfill the purposes for collecting the information, provided that any such third party will commit to protect your privacy as required under the applicable law and this policy.

We may share personal data with etailz’ corporate affiliates. These companies use your information as described in this Privacy Policy.

We may share personal data with law enforcement, government agencies, courts, or other organizations: (a) as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena or similar legal process; or (b) when etailz believes in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request.

We may share or transfer personal data if etailz is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, as part of such transaction. In any event, your information will remain protected under this Privacy Policy.

We may share it in any other circumstances where etailz receives your written consent.  

### RETENTION OF PERSONAL DATA

We keep your information for the time period required to complete the purposes for which it is processed or satisfy legal requirements. The length of time for which we retain information depends on the purposes for which we collected and use it or the requirements of applicable laws.  

### OPT-IN CHOICES & LEGAL RIGHTS

You will be given an opportunity to opt-in to targeted communications from etailz. If you opt-out, etailz will only respond to direct inquiries and will not use your personal information to contact you for any other purpose.

Furthermore, you have the legal right to:

  * Access the data that we keep about you. We may need to ask you to provide us certain credentials to make sure that you are who you claim you are. If you find that the data is not accurate, complete, or up-to-date, then you may provide us with the necessary information to rectify it.
  * Contact us if you want to withdraw your consent to the processing of your personal information. Exercising this right will not affect the lawfulness of processing based on consent before its withdrawal.
  * Request to delete or restrict access to your personal information. We may postpone or deny your request if your personal information is in current use for providing our services or to other legitimate purposes such as compliance with regulatory requirements associated with etailz.
  * You may ask to transfer your personal information in accordance with your right to data portability.
  * You may object to the processing of your personal information for direct marketing purposes.
  * You have the right not to be subject to a decision based solely on automated processing, including profiling, which produces legal effects concerning you or similarly significantly affecting you.
  * You have a right to lodge a complaint with a data protection supervisory authority.

If you exercise one (or more) of the above-mentioned rights, in accordance with the provisions of applicable law, you may request to be informed that third parties that hold your personal information, in accordance with this Policy, will act accordingly.

We do periodic assessments of our data processing and privacy practices to ensure that we comply with this Privacy Policy, to update this Privacy Policy when needed, and to verify that this Privacy Policy is displayed properly and is accessible.

If you have any concerns about the way we process your personal information, you are welcome to contact [privacy@etailz.com](mailto:privacy@etailz.com).

We will investigate your inquiry and make good-faith efforts to resolve any existing or potential dispute with you. If you are unhappy with the response you receive and reside in the EU, you can also refer the matter to the Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO).  

### CHILDREN’S PRIVACY

We do not knowingly collect or solicit “personal information” (as defined by the U.S. Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act) from anyone under the age of 13. If you are under 13, please do not attempt to contact us or send any personal information about yourself to us. If we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13, we will delete that information. If you believe that a child under 13 may have provided us personal information, please contact us at [privacy@etailz.com](mailto:privacy@etailz.com).

For residents of the EU, where processing of personal data is based on consent, we will not knowingly engage in that processing for users under the age of consent established by applicable member or data protection law. If we learn that we are engaged in that processing with such users, we will halt such processing and will take reasonable measures to promptly remove applicable information from our records.  

### CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS

If you are a California resident, you may ask for a list of third parties that have received your information for direct marketing purposes during the previous calendar year. This list also contains the types of information shared. We provide this list at no cost. To make such a request, contact us at [privacy@etailz.com](mailto:privacy@etailz.com).  

### CONTACT INFORMATION

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy or etailz’ use of your data, please send a detailed message to [privacy@etailz.com](mailto:privacy@etailz.com). You may also write to us at:

etailz, Inc.  
2818 N. Sullivan Rd., Ste 130  
Spokane Valley, WA 99216  
United States  

Updated: May 25, 2018
